<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Migration on Fuzaze' Blog</title><link>http://localhost:8081/tags/migration/</link><description>Recent content in Migration on Fuzaze' Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>by Edip AKPINAR 2026</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:40:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:8081/tags/migration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Voyage of the Mothers: The Austronesian Expansion</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-voyage-of-the-mothers-the-austronesian-expansion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-voyage-of-the-mothers-the-austronesian-expansion/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Location: The Pacific Genome Institute, Honolulu Subject: Matrilocality and the &amp;ldquo;Polynesian Motif&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the Indo-European and Bantu expansions were stories of &amp;ldquo;Conquering Fathers,&amp;rdquo; the settlement of the Pacific is the story of &amp;ldquo;Voyaging Families,&amp;rdquo; anchored by a powerful, female-centric social structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Tane Maaka stood before a digital map of the Pacific Ocean—the &amp;ldquo;Blue Continent.&amp;rdquo; It was the largest habitable space on Earth, and 3,500 years ago, a group of Neolithic sailors decided to cross it.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Green Tsunami: The Bantu Expansion</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-green-tsunami-the-bantu-expansion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:37:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-green-tsunami-the-bantu-expansion/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Green Tsunami: The Bantu Expansion
Location: The Great Lakes Region, East Africa Subject: The Convergence of Iron, Blood, and Syntax&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the Indo-European expansion was a story of horses and chariots across the open steppe, the Bantu Expansion was a story of iron axes and yam roots cutting through the dense heart of the continent. It is arguably the greatest migration in human history, turning a small group of speakers in West Africa (modern-day Cameroon/Nigeria border) into the dominant demographic force of the southern half of the continent.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>