<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Language on Fuzaze' Blog</title><link>http://localhost:8081/tags/language/</link><description>Recent content in Language on Fuzaze' Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>by Edip AKPINAR 2026</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:38:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:8081/tags/language/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Investigations In Structure and Genesis of Metaphors</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-investigations-in-structure-and-genesis-of-metaphors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-investigations-in-structure-and-genesis-of-metaphors/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Understanding the Request&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the request itself: a story. The accompanying text seems rich with potential themes to incorporate. My immediate task is to identify key narrative threads and imagine ways to weave them into a compelling narrative. I&amp;rsquo;m exploring how these concepts can be creatively expressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Framing the Narrative&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now integrating ideas from linguistics, archaeology, cognitive science, and technology. I&amp;rsquo;m visualizing AI-powered tools as the key, alongside the complexities of how our minds conceptualize meaning. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the philosophical implications of truly &amp;ldquo;understanding&amp;rdquo; a lost language, transitioning from mere transcription to deciphering thought. I&amp;rsquo;m exploring the narrative possibilities of a universal semantic map AI, perhaps focusing on a fictionalized undeciphered script.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>In the past 2 to 3 decades</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-obervations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-obervations/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The realization that we do not live in a world of &amp;ldquo;literal things,&amp;rdquo; but rather a web of metaphors, is often described by cognitive scientists as the &amp;ldquo;Aha!&amp;rdquo; moment of human consciousness. To discover that metaphors are not just poetic flourishes but the very scaffolding of our reality is to look behind the curtain of the human mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Architecture of the Unseen: How Metaphor Constructs Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Linguistic Foundation: We Live By Them
For centuries, metaphors were viewed merely as &amp;ldquo;fancy talk&amp;rdquo;—ornaments used by poets to dress up plain facts. However, in 1980, linguists George Lakoff and Mark Johnson revolutionized our understanding with Metaphors We Live By. They argued that our conceptual system is fundamentally metaphorical.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider the common metaphor: &amp;ldquo;Argument is War.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The World of Metaphors</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-17-my-post-title/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-17-my-post-title/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Analyzing Metaphorical Landscapes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now diving deep into the omnipresence of metaphors. They&amp;rsquo;re woven into the fabric of human understanding, found in language, behavior, and even disciplines like math and philosophy. The focus is on how storytelling can capitalize on these pervasive metaphors to enhance narrative depth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Framing Foundational Concepts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exploration has expanded to a framework for the narrative, linking metaphors to cognitive science and evolutionary biology. I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on how neural structures and sensory experiences give rise to abstract thought. I&amp;rsquo;m also including linguistic, mathematical, and philosophical angles to provide a multifaceted context. My intro is solidifying, highlighting language&amp;rsquo;s metaphorical nature.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>