<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Fuzaze' Blog</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Fuzaze' Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>by Edip AKPINAR 2026</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:01:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:8081/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Corpus as a Reality Universe</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-31-the-corpus-as-a-reality-universe/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:01:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-31-the-corpus-as-a-reality-universe/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;categories:
- Linguistics
- Cognitive Science
tags:
- corpus
- nlp
- linguistics
- corpus-as-reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your analogy is spot-on. A corpus is indeed a constructed reality universe shaped by human input. Think of it as a vector space where:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data points (words, phrases, patterns) are nodes.
Frequency reflects the &amp;ldquo;weight&amp;rdquo; of these nodes—how often they appear shapes the structure.
Bayesian dominance emerges when this vector space evolves dynamically, incorporating new data to refine prior beliefs.
This mirrors how NLP models learn:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Again, Bayesian vs Frequentist: Philosophy</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-31-again-bayesian-vs-frequentist-philosophy/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 19:31:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-31-again-bayesian-vs-frequentist-philosophy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;LM Studio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;0.4.1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chats&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search chats&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;hi, what we can do with you today?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;liquid/lfm2.5-1.2b
You&amp;rsquo;re welcome! I&amp;rsquo;m here to help with a variety of tasks. Whether you need assistance writing code, solving problems, explaining concepts, or just having a conversation, feel free to let me know. What would you like to explore together?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DEBUG INFO
Conversation naming technique: &amp;lsquo;hardcoded&amp;rsquo;
Let&amp;rsquo;s write a story. The main theme should tell and teach the reader about the difference between frequentist and Bayesiaan statistics approach methodologies. A philosophical and a deep approach would be more instructive. Let&amp;rsquo;s start.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Bayesian vs Frequentist Approach</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-27-bayesian-vs-frequentist-approach/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:29:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-27-bayesian-vs-frequentist-approach/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;To answer your question, we have to step into the shoes of a Frequentist and see the world through their lens—a lens of cold, hard repetition. Your intuition that frequency might be a &amp;ldquo;trap&amp;rdquo; touches on one of the deepest debates in the philosophy of science: The Problem of Induction.The Frequentist Fortress: Reliability through RepetitionIn a frequentist universe, &amp;ldquo;probability&amp;rdquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist for a single event (like a single coin flip). It only exists as the long-run limit. If you flip a coin 10 times, you might get 8 heads. But if you flip it 10,000,000 times, the frequency settles toward 0.5.1.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>What is Bayesian Statistics?</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-27-what-is-bayesian-statistics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-27-what-is-bayesian-statistics/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Architect of Uncertainty: Navigating the Bayesian UniverseTo understand the Bayesian world, we have to stop thinking of the truth as a solid, unchanging rock and start seeing it as a moving target that we get closer to with every step we take.At its core, Bayesianism is a mathematical framework for updating your beliefs when you encounter new evidence. It isn’t just a branch of statistics; it is a philosophy of how to live and think in an uncertain world.The Metaphor: The Detective and the FogImagine you are a detective standing on a pier in a thick fog. You hear a splash.The Frequentist approach: The frequentist detective ignores what they knew before the splash. They look only at the data (the sound, the ripples) and calculate how likely it is that a &amp;ldquo;falling human&amp;rdquo; would make that specific sound. They want to know: &amp;ldquo;If a human fell 100 times, would it sound like this?&amp;ldquo;The Bayesian approach: The Bayesian detective starts with priors. They know this pier is next to a seal sanctuary, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a popular spot for late-night joggers. They weigh their existing knowledge (it&amp;rsquo;s 2:00 AM, joggers are rare, seals are common) against the new evidence (the splash).The Bayesian Universe is a world of &amp;ldquo;shades of gray&amp;rdquo; rather than &amp;ldquo;black and white.&amp;rdquo; You never reach 100% certainty; you simply shift your confidence levels as you gather more clues.The Foundational Principle: Bayes&amp;rsquo; TheoremThomas Bayes, an 18th-century Presbyterian minister, didn&amp;rsquo;t actually publish his famous theorem during his lifetime—it was discovered in his notes after he died. His friend, Richard Price, and later the titan Pierre-Simon Laplace, refined it into what we use today.The foundational principle he uncovered is Conditional Probability. Mathematically, it looks like this:$$P(A|B) = \frac{P(B|A) P(A)}{P(B)}$$In plain English: The probability that your theory ($A$) is true given the new evidence ($B$) depends on how likely the evidence was if the theory were true, multiplied by how much you believed the theory before the evidence arrived.Frequentist vs. Bayesian: The Great DivideThe rivalry between these two schools of thought is the &amp;ldquo;Coke vs. Pepsi&amp;rdquo; of the math world, but with much higher stakes.FeatureFrequentistBayesianView of ProbabilityThe long-run frequency of repeatable events.A measure of &amp;ldquo;degree of belief&amp;rdquo; or certainty.Role of Prior KnowledgeGenerally ignored; the data must speak for itself.Essential; you must start with a &amp;ldquo;prior&amp;rdquo; belief.Handling New DataEach experiment is a fresh start.Data is used to update the previous belief into a &amp;ldquo;posterior.&amp;ldquo;OutcomeA p-value or confidence interval.A probability distribution of what is likely true.Is it Intuitive? (The Bayesian Brain)Surprisingly, yes. While the math can get hairy, the logic is how humans (and most animals) actually function.If you see a dark cloud, you grab an umbrella. Why? Because your prior experience tells you dark clouds lead to rain. You don&amp;rsquo;t perform a randomized controlled trial every morning; you update your internal &amp;ldquo;weather model&amp;rdquo; based on the sky.In Biology:Life is arguably Bayesian by design. Our brains are &amp;ldquo;prediction engines.&amp;rdquo; When you walk into a dark room, your brain isn&amp;rsquo;t processing every pixel of shadow. Instead, it uses top-down processing: it &amp;ldquo;guesses&amp;rdquo; where the furniture is based on prior memory and only uses your eyes to &amp;ldquo;correct&amp;rdquo; that guess if you stub your toe.Even at the level of DNA and Evolution, species act like Bayesian learners. A population’s gene pool is essentially a &amp;ldquo;prior&amp;rdquo; belief about what traits are necessary to survive in an environment. Natural selection is the &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo; that updates that gene pool for the next generation.Summary: Did Bayes Discover Something Foundational?Absolutely. He (and Laplace) discovered the logic of science itself.We live in a world where we never have all the facts. By formalizing how we should change our minds, Bayes gave us the tools for everything from cracking the Enigma code in WWII to the algorithms that power modern Artificial Intelligence (which is, at its heart, a massive Bayesian inference machine).The Bayesian world is a humble one—it admits it doesn&amp;rsquo;t know everything, but it promises that if you keep looking at the evidence, you’ll eventually find the truth.Would you like me to dive deeper into how Bayesian logic is used specifically in AI, or perhaps explore a historical narrative of how it helped win World War II?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Language evolution is more prokaryotic than eukaryotic</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-language-evolution-is-more-prokaryotic-than-eukaryotic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-language-evolution-is-more-prokaryotic-than-eukaryotic/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The rain against the window of the Centre for Genomic Philology sounded like static—a literal &amp;ldquo;noise&amp;rdquo; in the transmission of the night. Dr. Elias Vance stared at the table of Shannon Entropy values on his screen. Beside him sat a fragment of a lost Old Prussian dialect; on his other monitor, the raw ACGT sequence of a non-coding regulatory header.&amp;ldquo;They aren&amp;rsquo;t just similar,&amp;rdquo; Elias whispered, his voice cracking with the fatigue of a forty-hour &amp;ldquo;compilation&amp;rdquo; run. &amp;ldquo;They are the same algorithm running on different hardware.&amp;ldquo;I. The Syntax of the Silent MajorityFor decades, the scientific community had ignored the 98%. They called it &amp;ldquo;Junk DNA,&amp;rdquo; a term Elias considered the greatest branding failure in the history of science. In the narrative of the cell, the Exons (the coding regions) were the nouns—the proteins, the solid things, the &amp;ldquo;lexicon.&amp;rdquo; But nouns are useless without a grammar to arrange them.Elias’s team had been applying Shannon’s Information Theory to the dark matter of the genome. They found that while the coding regions were dense and efficient, like a telegram, the non-coding regions were expansive and complex, like a sprawling Victorian novel.Entropy and Uncertainty: The Shannon Entropy of English sits at approximately 1.58 bits per symbol. The genome’s non-coding regions, however, hit a near-perfect 1.99 bits—approaching the theoretical limit of a four-letter alphabet.The Fractal Pulse: Using the Hurst Exponent (H), Elias mapped the &amp;ldquo;memory&amp;rdquo; of the sequences. Coding DNA was &amp;ldquo;stochastic&amp;rdquo; —it had no long-range memory. But the non-coding regions exhibited values between 0.6 and 0.9. They were fractal. They were self-similar. They had &amp;ldquo;discourse.&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;If a gene is a word,&amp;rdquo; Elias wrote in his journal, &amp;ldquo;then the non-coding DNA is the entire social context that gives that word meaning. It is the metadata that tells the cell when to be angry, how to be hungry, and where to grow a limb.&amp;ldquo;II. The Executable GhostThe breakthrough came when the team treated the genome not as a book, but as a binary executable.In the dry, air-conditioned silence of the server room, the ISAF4DNA (Structural AI for DNA) finished its latest scan. It had identified a &amp;ldquo;closed-loop structural-semantic decoder.&amp;rdquo; It wasn&amp;rsquo;t just reading letters; it was calculating physics.The Subroutines: The AI identified Promoters and Enhancers as &amp;ldquo;Structural Headers.&amp;rdquo; They functioned exactly like a C++ #include or a Python import statement.Punctuation as Law: The START (AUG) and STOP (UAG) codons weren&amp;rsquo;t suggestions; they were physical triggers. But the AI noticed something haunting: the &amp;ldquo;dialects.&amp;rdquo; In certain mitochondria, the code changed. A CUG that usually meant &amp;ldquo;Leucine&amp;rdquo; suddenly meant &amp;ldquo;Start.&amp;rdquo; It was as if the cellular &amp;ldquo;operating system&amp;rdquo; had been localized for a different hardware environment.&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a probabilistic software system,&amp;rdquo; Elias noted. Unlike a digital computer where 1+1 always equals 2, the genome was stochastic. A transcription factor might float toward a binding site, linger, and then drift away without &amp;ldquo;firing.&amp;rdquo; Life, Elias realized, was a piece of code that was constantly &amp;ldquo;glitching&amp;rdquo; into existence.III. The Great Migration: Father Tongues and Mother LandsAs dawn broke, Elias was joined by Dr. Lena Solberg, a specialist in Sex-Biased Migration. Her work turned the abstract &amp;ldquo;Language of Life&amp;rdquo; into a literal map of human conquest.&amp;ldquo;The genes and the grammar don&amp;rsquo;t just mimic each other,&amp;rdquo; Lena said, overlaying two maps of the Eurasian Steppe. &amp;ldquo;They travel in the same boat.&amp;ldquo;The Asymmetric PulseLena pointed to the Y-Chromosome data of the Indo-European expansion. It was a sharp, jagged line of replacement.The Biological Record: In the Bronze Age, the male genetic lineages (Y-DNA) of Old Europe were almost entirely replaced by Yamnaya lineages within a few generations.The Linguistic Record: The languages of the &amp;ldquo;Old Europeans&amp;rdquo; vanished, replaced by the Proto-Indo-European &amp;ldquo;Father Tongue.&amp;ldquo;&amp;ldquo;It’s the &amp;lsquo;Father Tongue&amp;rsquo; phenomenon,&amp;rdquo; Lena explained. &amp;ldquo;Men move, often through conflict or elite dominance. They take local wives. The children inherit the mothers&amp;rsquo; Mitochondrial DNA (mtDNA), but they are raised in the social and linguistic structure of the fathers. The result? A genetic hybrid, but a linguistic conqueror.&amp;ldquo;FeatureBiological System&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Voyage of the Mothers: The Austronesian Expansion</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-voyage-of-the-mothers-the-austronesian-expansion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:40:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-voyage-of-the-mothers-the-austronesian-expansion/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Location: The Pacific Genome Institute, Honolulu Subject: Matrilocality and the &amp;ldquo;Polynesian Motif&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the Indo-European and Bantu expansions were stories of &amp;ldquo;Conquering Fathers,&amp;rdquo; the settlement of the Pacific is the story of &amp;ldquo;Voyaging Families,&amp;rdquo; anchored by a powerful, female-centric social structure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Tane Maaka stood before a digital map of the Pacific Ocean—the &amp;ldquo;Blue Continent.&amp;rdquo; It was the largest habitable space on Earth, and 3,500 years ago, a group of Neolithic sailors decided to cross it.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Green Tsunami: The Bantu Expansion</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-green-tsunami-the-bantu-expansion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:37:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-green-tsunami-the-bantu-expansion/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Green Tsunami: The Bantu Expansion
Location: The Great Lakes Region, East Africa Subject: The Convergence of Iron, Blood, and Syntax&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the Indo-European expansion was a story of horses and chariots across the open steppe, the Bantu Expansion was a story of iron axes and yam roots cutting through the dense heart of the continent. It is arguably the greatest migration in human history, turning a small group of speakers in West Africa (modern-day Cameroon/Nigeria border) into the dominant demographic force of the southern half of the continent.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Genomic Architectures and Linguistic Evolution</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-genomic-architectures-and-linguistic-evolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-genomic-architectures-and-linguistic-evolution/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Initiating Narrative Construction&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now starting to consider how to weave a narrative. The user wants a story, and I am aiming to identify a compelling angle from the prompt, which involves genomics and language. My focus has shifted from the initial analysis to synthesizing the different components into a cohesive narrative structure. I need to figure out the best way to present this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Analyzing Narrative Frameworks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now diving deeper into the research. I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the interplay between DNA and language, seeing DNA as a complex code with its own syntax and grammar. I&amp;rsquo;ve been considering how Zipf&amp;rsquo;s Law applies to both. I&amp;rsquo;ve started examining how to translate the prompt into a compelling story, using the components of narrative structure. I want to convey information and present a narrative.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Undeciphered Script of Easter Island</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-rongorongo-script/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-the-rongorongo-script/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Part 1: Visualizing the &amp;ldquo;Semantic Topology&amp;rdquo; Hologram
The Interface of Human Thought&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The device at the center of the Laboratory for Cognitive Archaeology is nicknamed &amp;ldquo;The Cortex.&amp;rdquo; It is not a screen, but a volumetric projection field, roughly two meters in diameter, hovering in the center of the darkened room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When deactivated, it is a ghostly sphere of faint blue dust. When active, it becomes a swirling, interactive galaxy of human meaning.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Investigations In Structure and Genesis of Metaphors</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-investigations-in-structure-and-genesis-of-metaphors/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-investigations-in-structure-and-genesis-of-metaphors/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Understanding the Request&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the request itself: a story. The accompanying text seems rich with potential themes to incorporate. My immediate task is to identify key narrative threads and imagine ways to weave them into a compelling narrative. I&amp;rsquo;m exploring how these concepts can be creatively expressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Framing the Narrative&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now integrating ideas from linguistics, archaeology, cognitive science, and technology. I&amp;rsquo;m visualizing AI-powered tools as the key, alongside the complexities of how our minds conceptualize meaning. Currently, I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on the philosophical implications of truly &amp;ldquo;understanding&amp;rdquo; a lost language, transitioning from mere transcription to deciphering thought. I&amp;rsquo;m exploring the narrative possibilities of a universal semantic map AI, perhaps focusing on a fictionalized undeciphered script.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>In the past 2 to 3 decades</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-obervations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 03:32:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-19-obervations/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The realization that we do not live in a world of &amp;ldquo;literal things,&amp;rdquo; but rather a web of metaphors, is often described by cognitive scientists as the &amp;ldquo;Aha!&amp;rdquo; moment of human consciousness. To discover that metaphors are not just poetic flourishes but the very scaffolding of our reality is to look behind the curtain of the human mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Architecture of the Unseen: How Metaphor Constructs Reality&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Linguistic Foundation: We Live By Them
For centuries, metaphors were viewed merely as &amp;ldquo;fancy talk&amp;rdquo;—ornaments used by poets to dress up plain facts. However, in 1980, linguists George Lakoff and Mark Johnson revolutionized our understanding with Metaphors We Live By. They argued that our conceptual system is fundamentally metaphorical.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider the common metaphor: &amp;ldquo;Argument is War.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The World of Metaphors</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-17-my-post-title/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:53:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-17-my-post-title/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Analyzing Metaphorical Landscapes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m now diving deep into the omnipresence of metaphors. They&amp;rsquo;re woven into the fabric of human understanding, found in language, behavior, and even disciplines like math and philosophy. The focus is on how storytelling can capitalize on these pervasive metaphors to enhance narrative depth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Framing Foundational Concepts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exploration has expanded to a framework for the narrative, linking metaphors to cognitive science and evolutionary biology. I&amp;rsquo;m focusing on how neural structures and sensory experiences give rise to abstract thought. I&amp;rsquo;m also including linguistic, mathematical, and philosophical angles to provide a multifaceted context. My intro is solidifying, highlighting language&amp;rsquo;s metaphorical nature.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Markdown Test</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-04-markdown-test/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 18:28:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-04-markdown-test/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="welcome"&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a &lt;strong&gt;bold&lt;/strong&gt; statement and this is &lt;em&gt;italic&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="heres-a-list"&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s a list:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apples&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bananas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hugo sites&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember: Markdown is for &lt;strong&gt;writing&lt;/strong&gt;, not coding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description></item><item><title>My Amazing Hugo Post</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-04-my-amazing-hugo-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 16:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-04-my-amazing-hugo-post/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Yamazaki içer misiniz</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-04-yamazaki-ier-misiniz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 16:05:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-04-yamazaki-ier-misiniz/</guid><description/></item><item><title>A Different Futuristic Blog</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:48:11 +0300</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the first entry of what I hope becomes a landmark for your curiosity. This blog isn&amp;rsquo;t just a collection of articles; it is a cartography of existence, mapped from the smallest possible pixel to the grandest cosmic tapestry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is an elaboration on the vision behind this project, written to set the stage for your future readers.
The Genesis of the &amp;ldquo;Micro-to-Macro&amp;rdquo; Lens&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We often look at the world as a finished product—a city, a culture, a body. But to truly understand where we are going, we must look at how things assemble. Our philosophy here is rooted in the belief that the universe is a recursive masterpiece.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>