<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Bayesian on Fuzaze' Blog</title><link>http://localhost:8081/tags/bayesian/</link><description>Recent content in Bayesian on Fuzaze' Blog</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>by Edip AKPINAR 2026</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:20:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:8081/tags/bayesian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>What is Bayesian Statistics?</title><link>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-27-what-is-bayesian-statistics/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:20:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:8081/posts/2026-01-27-what-is-bayesian-statistics/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The Architect of Uncertainty: Navigating the Bayesian UniverseTo understand the Bayesian world, we have to stop thinking of the truth as a solid, unchanging rock and start seeing it as a moving target that we get closer to with every step we take.At its core, Bayesianism is a mathematical framework for updating your beliefs when you encounter new evidence. It isn’t just a branch of statistics; it is a philosophy of how to live and think in an uncertain world.The Metaphor: The Detective and the FogImagine you are a detective standing on a pier in a thick fog. You hear a splash.The Frequentist approach: The frequentist detective ignores what they knew before the splash. They look only at the data (the sound, the ripples) and calculate how likely it is that a &amp;ldquo;falling human&amp;rdquo; would make that specific sound. They want to know: &amp;ldquo;If a human fell 100 times, would it sound like this?&amp;ldquo;The Bayesian approach: The Bayesian detective starts with priors. They know this pier is next to a seal sanctuary, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a popular spot for late-night joggers. They weigh their existing knowledge (it&amp;rsquo;s 2:00 AM, joggers are rare, seals are common) against the new evidence (the splash).The Bayesian Universe is a world of &amp;ldquo;shades of gray&amp;rdquo; rather than &amp;ldquo;black and white.&amp;rdquo; You never reach 100% certainty; you simply shift your confidence levels as you gather more clues.The Foundational Principle: Bayes&amp;rsquo; TheoremThomas Bayes, an 18th-century Presbyterian minister, didn&amp;rsquo;t actually publish his famous theorem during his lifetime—it was discovered in his notes after he died. His friend, Richard Price, and later the titan Pierre-Simon Laplace, refined it into what we use today.The foundational principle he uncovered is Conditional Probability. Mathematically, it looks like this:$$P(A|B) = \frac{P(B|A) P(A)}{P(B)}$$In plain English: The probability that your theory ($A$) is true given the new evidence ($B$) depends on how likely the evidence was if the theory were true, multiplied by how much you believed the theory before the evidence arrived.Frequentist vs. Bayesian: The Great DivideThe rivalry between these two schools of thought is the &amp;ldquo;Coke vs. Pepsi&amp;rdquo; of the math world, but with much higher stakes.FeatureFrequentistBayesianView of ProbabilityThe long-run frequency of repeatable events.A measure of &amp;ldquo;degree of belief&amp;rdquo; or certainty.Role of Prior KnowledgeGenerally ignored; the data must speak for itself.Essential; you must start with a &amp;ldquo;prior&amp;rdquo; belief.Handling New DataEach experiment is a fresh start.Data is used to update the previous belief into a &amp;ldquo;posterior.&amp;ldquo;OutcomeA p-value or confidence interval.A probability distribution of what is likely true.Is it Intuitive? (The Bayesian Brain)Surprisingly, yes. While the math can get hairy, the logic is how humans (and most animals) actually function.If you see a dark cloud, you grab an umbrella. Why? Because your prior experience tells you dark clouds lead to rain. You don&amp;rsquo;t perform a randomized controlled trial every morning; you update your internal &amp;ldquo;weather model&amp;rdquo; based on the sky.In Biology:Life is arguably Bayesian by design. Our brains are &amp;ldquo;prediction engines.&amp;rdquo; When you walk into a dark room, your brain isn&amp;rsquo;t processing every pixel of shadow. Instead, it uses top-down processing: it &amp;ldquo;guesses&amp;rdquo; where the furniture is based on prior memory and only uses your eyes to &amp;ldquo;correct&amp;rdquo; that guess if you stub your toe.Even at the level of DNA and Evolution, species act like Bayesian learners. A population’s gene pool is essentially a &amp;ldquo;prior&amp;rdquo; belief about what traits are necessary to survive in an environment. Natural selection is the &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo; that updates that gene pool for the next generation.Summary: Did Bayes Discover Something Foundational?Absolutely. He (and Laplace) discovered the logic of science itself.We live in a world where we never have all the facts. By formalizing how we should change our minds, Bayes gave us the tools for everything from cracking the Enigma code in WWII to the algorithms that power modern Artificial Intelligence (which is, at its heart, a massive Bayesian inference machine).The Bayesian world is a humble one—it admits it doesn&amp;rsquo;t know everything, but it promises that if you keep looking at the evidence, you’ll eventually find the truth.Would you like me to dive deeper into how Bayesian logic is used specifically in AI, or perhaps explore a historical narrative of how it helped win World War II?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>